Martin P. Catherwood Library Circulation Department Reserve Lists /4006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Circulation Department Reserve Lists
1967- 1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
/4006
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Consists of list of materials placed on reserve by the faculty, arranged by semester.
3082599
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 21, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4012: Kheel Center Files and Circulation Reserve List /4044: Martin P. Catherwood Library Circulation Department Reserve Reading List Additional /4035: Martin P. Catherwood Library Exchange Bibliographies /4214: Martin P. Catherwood Library Phase I Security Documents
Martin P. Catherwood Library.
3082599
- Summer Reserves 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Spring 1968 A-L (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Spring 1968 M-Z (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Summer Reserves 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Fall 1968 A-Z (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Spring 1969 A-L (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Spring 1969 M-Z (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Fall 1969 A-L (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Fall 1969 M-Z (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Spring 1970 A-L (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Spring 1970 M-Z (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Fall 1970 A-L (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Fall 1970 M-Z (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Spring 1971 A-L (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Spring 1971 M-Z (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Summer Reserves 1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Fall 1971 A-L (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Fall 1971 M-Z (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Fall 1972 M-Z (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Fall 1972 A-L (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Spring 1972 M-Z (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Spring 1972 A-L (Box 2, Folder 6)